dailytimes.ng 2018-01-30

# Privacy Policy — Daily Times Nigeria

## Privacy Policy  
Daily Times of Nigeria Plc 

### Privacy Policy for use of www.dailytimes.ng Site

Daily Times of Nigeria Plc is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This Privacy Policy explains how we use the information we collect about you and procedures we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

In this Privacy Policy references to we, us and our, are to Daily Times of Nigeria Plc . References to the Site are to www.dailytimes.ng and any of the ‘DAILYTIMES’ branded sites or microsites, such as www.DAILYTIMES.ng etc.

Certain expressions used in this Privacy Policy (such as User Content) have definitions which are set out in the Terms and Conditions for use of this Site.

### 1\. What Information we Collect

The information we collect via the Site may include:

1.1 Personal details you give us through completion of forms on the Website, including name, address, telephone number, email address etc.

1.2 Debit or credit card information which we need to pass to a bank or card processing agency for verification.

1.3 Your IP address, your preferences and use of email updates.

1.4 Data recorded by the Site which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings. Such data is recorded locally on your computer through the use of cookies. Your browser can be programmed to reject cookies or warn you before downloading them. However some features of the Site may not function properly if you programme your browser to reject cookies.

1.5 When you use the Site our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. This may include your web request, internet protocol address, browser type, browser language, URL’s, URL’s domain names, pages viewed and other matters together with cookies which may identify your browser.

###  2\. What we do with your Information

Any personal information we collect from the Site we use for some or all of the following purposes:

2.1 To process your registration and provide you the features and functionality of the Site.

2.2 Personal information or text, photo or video content that you post as part of your User Content becomes publicly available and can be viewed and used by others. Your account name (but not your email address) is displayed to other users when you use the Site or send messages through the Site and other users can contact you by sending messages through the Site. Any text, photos or videos that you submit to the Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media and may be viewed by the public.

2.3 In some cases we may use your email address to send you information on other products and services. You will be offered the option to opt out of such service.

2.4 We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities such as processing and sorting data, monitoring use of the Site etc. Such third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

2.5 We may use aggregated information for the purpose of monitoring use of the Site. Such aggregated information may be provided to third parties. These statistics will not include information which can be used to identify any individual.

2.6 We may provide personal data to carefully selected third parties for commercial or marketing use where we believe such third parties provide goods or services which may be of interest to you. You may opt out of such service. We can supply a complete list of third parties to whom personal data is supplied upon request.

### 3\. Links

3.1 As a User you may have access to a specific part of the Site where your User Content may be posted. We will agree with you which personnel may access certain areas of the Site.

3.2 The Site may contain links to other sites. Please note that we are not responsible for the Privacy Policies or practices of other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave the Site and to read the Privacy Policies of other sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on the Site.

### 4\. Protection of Information

4.1 The internet is not a secure medium. However, we have put in place recommended up to date security measures and will review these and keep them updated regularly.

4.2 Subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we keep your information confidential. To ensure that we are able to maintain confidentiality you must comply with the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Site.

4.3 You agree not to collect any personal information on other living individuals by your access to User Content posted by others upon the Site.

### 5\. Updating/Modification

5.1 If any of the details you have provided the Site changes, please give us correct details by email to: admin@dailytimes.ng

5.2 We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without notice. The new Privacy Policy will be posted upon the Site and your continued use of the Site will be considered acceptance of it. You are advised to check this Privacy Policy regularly.

### 6\. Your Consent

6.1 By submitting your information on the Site, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If we change the Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this page and we may place notices on other pages of the Site so that you may be aware of such change. Your continued use of the Site will then signify that you agree to such changes.

6.2 Owing to the global nature of the internet, the information you provide may be transferred to companies outside the European Economic Area (EEA) that do not have similar protections in place to those which apply in the EEA regarding your data and its use as set out in this Policy. However, we have taken steps outlined in this Policy to protect the security of your information and will keep any transfers outside the EEA to a necessary minimum. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers.

### 7\. Data Subject Requests

7.1 We are the Data Controller in respect of personal data submitted to you in respect of the Site for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, England.

7.2 If you wish to update the personal information or make a subject access request please email the admin@dailytimes.ng

7.3 This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions for use of this Site which are situated elsewhere on the Site.

## Copyright Complaints

Daily Times of Nigeria Plc  
www.dailytimes.ng  Site, and any of the ‘DAILYTIMES’ branded sites or microsites, such as www.DAILYTIMES.ng.

### Copyright Infringement Notification

If you see material on the Site which you consider is an infringement of any copyright to which you claim to be entitled in accordance with the Copyrights, Patents and Designs Act 1988, England (as amended) please contact us at the address stated below to notify us of the alleged infringement and in doing so complying with the following requirements.  Please supply:

  1. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorised to act on behalf of the copyright owner.
  2. Identification of the copyright work that you claim has been infringed.
  3. Definitive identification of the copyright material that you claim has been infringed and which you wish to have removed from the Site.  Providing a complete URL in the body of an email is the best way to help us locate such material quickly.
  4. Full information regarding the complainant including: 
    1. Name (and company number and place of incorporation if appropriate).
    2. Address.
    3. Telephone and email contact.
    4. A statement that the complainant owns the copyright material or is duly authorised to make this complaint on behalf of an identified copyright owner.
  5. A statement that the information in the notification is accurate to the best of the providers knowledge and belief and that the complainant is authorised to act on behalf of the owner of the claimed copyright material.

Your written notice should be sent by email to: admin@dailytimes.ng

Or in writing to:

HEAD OFFICE:  
3, Imam Augusto Close,  
Off Olosa Street,  
Victoria Island,  
Lagos

OPERATIONAL OFFICE:  
5, Lateef Jakande Road,  
Agidingbi – Ikeja,  
Lagos

We will take reasonable steps to remove copyright material from the Site where complete and accurate information is submitted in respect of the alleged copyright infringement.  You are not entitled to submit a copyright infringement notification where you do not own or are not authorised to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright material.  Such an action may render you liable to legal action by the true owner of the copyright material.

(Visited 11 times, 1 visits today)
